HAEMIN RYU



Seoul, South Korea

(GPA: 3.56/4.0)

My vision is to enrich and diversify the interaction between users and computers by creating novel experiences with emerging technology to make products accessible to people, regardless of disability and age.

My interests rest at the intersection of Human-Computer Interaction (HCI), Universal Design, VR, and Accessibility.

EDUCATION

Purdue University B. S. in Computer Science

Jan. 2018-Dec. 2019

Fort Wayne, IN, USA (GPA: 3.71/4.0)

Seoul Women's University B. E. in Computer Science

Mar. 2014-Feb. 2020

Honors: Full-ride Merit-based Scholar, Dual Degree Program Scholar

Honors: Top 50, Dual Degree Program Scholar

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer Cirrus ABS Corporation (MarketSnare)

Jan. 2020-Present

- Delivered a local marketing web platform 'MarketSnare' that meets multi-location business needs with centralized management, localization, and customization for various regions.
- Developed web solutions with the MarketSnare software platforms using the Microsoft ASP.NET framework, C#, XML, XSLT, JSON, HTML/CSS/JS, API integrations, Database management, and Web Server Technologies.
- Highlighted projects: A&L Great Lakes Laboratories, Anthem Retail Program, ADT localized sites, Service Experts, IWDC

RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

[2] Menu interfaces to Avoid Disembodiment Situations in Virtual Reality

Advisor: Dr. Beomjin Kim 2022-Present

- Analyzed different menu styles environment to investigate the way to help improve menu interface design in Virtual Reality focused on the disembodiment issue.
- Conducted a test for menu interfaces in a Virtual Reality environment with a young age group and compared the result with the expectation of menu efficiency.

[1] Improvement to Pix2Code using Fast.ai: Automatic Generation of GUI with a Model Classification

Jan. 2020-Apr. 2020

Advisor: Dr. Venkata Inukollu - Demonstrated that automated deep learning model classification using Fast.ai can improve the accuracy and speed of the Pix2Code GUI Generation.

SELECTED PROJECTS

[2] PLUR: Online Platform for Physical Education Community for Individuals with Disabilities

#Accessibility #Sports #Community -Oct. 2021

- Created a web app that uses local resources and crowdsourcing to make sports programs and facilities more accessible to individuals with disabilities.
- Developed scenarios for connecting differently abled children and young adults with verified local coaches, trainers, sports associations, and clubs to begin their journey in sports.

[1] Indoor Navigation: Improved Accessibility for People with Disabilities

FUNDED BY * PARKVIEW

#Accessibility #DataVisualization #Navigation #Hospital

Aug. 2019-Apr. 2020

- Leveraged hospital navigation data from beacon technology focused on the patient experience to provide a more accessible hospital visit experience for patients with disabilities.
- Designed a data analytics web application to discover heavy/light usage facilities and routes at the hospital and improved mobile application navigation to assist patients.
- Built a web interface that visualizes interactive data analytics and displays employee administration management systems using Angular 7, TypeScript, and HTML/CSS/JS.

AWARDS AND HONORS

Academic Conferences

Oct. 2022	ACM UIST Travel Award	ACM UIST 2022, USD 1,338
Jul. 2020	IEEE/ACM ICSE 2020 Student Mentoring Workshop	IEEE/ACM ASE 2019, USD 500
Oct. 2019	Student Travel Fund Grant for IEEE/ACM ASE 2019	Purdue Global, USD 1,164.83

Scholastic Achievements

Apr. 2019Purdue Fort Wayne Top 50 AwardPurdue FW Top 50 Committee2018, 2019Dean's List & Semester Honors ListPurdue FW College of ETCS2018, 2019Dual Degree Program Scholarship, 2-year Full TuitionSWU Division of International Affairs2014, 2015Seoul Women's University Merit-based Scholarship, 2-semester Full TuitionSWU College of Informatics & Media	Apr. 2020	Student Research and Creative Endeavor Symposium - Poster	Purdue FW Research & Innovation
2018, 2019 Dual Degree Program Scholarship, 2-year Full Tuition SWU Division of International Affairs	Apr. 2019	Purdue Fort Wayne Top 50 Award	Purdue FW Top 50 Committee
2010, 2013 Dual Degree Hogram Scholarship, 2-year full fullion	2018, 2019	Dean's List & Semester Honors List	Purdue FW College of ETCS
2014, 2015 Seoul Women's University Merit-based Scholarship, 2-semester Full Tuition SWU College of Informatics & Media	2018, 2019	Dual Degree Program Scholarship, 2-year Full Tuition	SWU Division of International Affairs
	2014, 2015	Seoul Women's University Merit-based Scholarship, 2-semester Full Tuition	SWU College of Informatics & Media

Collaborative Project Achievements

Oct. 2021	Hack for Humanity - Top 7 Finalist	Arizona State University & StateFarm
Feb. 2021	Flipping Finance Challenge - 1 st & 2 nd Places	Indiana Bond Bank, USD 270
May. 2019	Senior Capstone Design Project Excellence Award - 2 nd Place	Purdue FW Dept. of Computer Science
Nov. 2015	Creative Idea Competition Award - 1st Place	SWU Creative Center, USD 279
Jul. 2015	LIKELION Ideathon - Top 10 Out of 110 projects & 500 college students	LIKELION

INVITED TALKS AND PANELS

Speaker		
Apr. 8th, 2022	UX Design for Web Developers	University of Illinois Web Conference

_		-
Pa	ne	əle

Nov. 28th, 2022	CS Mixer Event Alumni Panel	Purdue FW Dept. of Computer Science
Apr. 15th, 2022	Q & A with Engineering, Technology & Computer Science Alumni	Purdue FW College of ETCS
Apr. 12th, 2021	Engineering, Technology & Computer Science Internship Panel	Purdue FW International Week
Nov. 20th, 2019	"A Day in their Shoes" Simulation with Panel Discussion	

Guest Lecture

Oct. 2021	Journey on Conference	on Automated Software Engineering	Purdue FW Software Engineering class
-----------	-----------------------	-----------------------------------	--------------------------------------

VOLUNTEERING AND TEACHING

Academic Service

Oct. 2022, 2021, 2020	ACM UIST 2022, 2021, 2020 Student Volunteer
May. 2021	ACM CHI 2021 Student Volunteer
Jul. 2020	IEEE/ACM ICSE 2020 Student Volunteer

UX/UI Designer

Aug. 2021–Mar. 2022	United Nations SDSN Global Youth Seed Fund Initiative
Aug. 2021-Oct. 2021	Go Laadli Lead Like a Girl Challenge Project for Young Women Leaders

Leadership

Feb. 2020	ACM Global Game Jam Fort Wayne Site Organizer
Jul. 2017–Aug. 2017	Dongan Intellectual and Developmental Disabilities Retreat Voluntee

Teaching Assistant

Fall 2018–Fall 2019	[CS 36000] Software Engineering with Professor. Venkata Inukollu
Summer 2019	[CS 16000] Intro to Computer Science I (Java) with Professor. David Liu

Tutoring

Fall 2018–Spring 2019	Core Academic Skills Assessment (CASA) - Mathematics
Mar. 2016–Nov. 2016	NAVER Connect Fdn. Play with Software - Programming education for elementary school students